Narrator: a
Speaker: John is Richard’s grandfather.
Narrator: 8
Speaker: Jennifer is Richard’s grandmother.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: Carol is Richard’s mother.
Narrator: 1
Speaker: Gary is Richard’s father.
Narrator: 9
Speaker: Sue is Richard’s aunt.
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Nick is Richard’s uncle.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: Kate is Richard’s sister.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: Steven is Richard’s brother.
Narrator: 13
Speaker: Hugh is Richard’s cousin.
Speaker: Sarah is Richard’s cousin.
Narrator: 14
Speaker: Emma is Richard’s wife.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: Chloe is Richard’s daughter.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: Jake is Richard’s son.
Narrator: 12
Speaker: Ruby is Richard’s niece.
Narrator: 11
Speaker: Oliver is Richard’s nephew.
Narrator: b
Speaker 1: my father and my mother: my parents
Narrator: 2
Speaker 2: my wife’s mother and father: my parents-in-law
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: my grandfather and my grandmother: my grandparents
Narrator: 4
Speaker 2: my son and my daughter: my children
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: a husband and wife: a couple